<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ScalHive LLC on ScalHive DEV</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ScalHive LLC on ScalHive DEV</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 10:02:57 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contacts-form/field_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contacts-form/field_1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Platform Engineers: Catalysts for Organizational Growth</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page-services/section-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page-services/section-1/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s data-driven world, Data Platform Engineers are not just in demand—they are essential. They are the architects and custodians of the foundational infrastructure that empowers data engineers to collect, store, and process vital organizational data.&#xA;Choosing the right Data Platform Engineer can be transformative for your data operations. Our engineers excel in:&#xA;Enhancing data collection and storage efficiency Accelerating data processing capabilities Elevating data analysis effectiveness Informing more insightful, data-driven decisions At ScalHive, we excel in identifying, vetting, and integrating elite Data Platform Engineers into your team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our vision</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page-index-first/section-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page-index-first/section-1/</guid>
      <description>Technology works for you, not the other way around. While others protected proprietary, stand-alone architectures, we focused on taking companies into the data-driven age, providing systems and software with the scalability and reliability needed to drive the future marketplace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScalHive: Pioneering Software Solutions Since 2015</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page-about-us/section-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page-about-us/section-1/</guid>
      <description>Founded in Ukraine, ScalHive has rapidly established itself as a beacon of innovation in software development. We are a vibrant team of young, forward-thinking professionals, including PhDs, MScs, and BScs, dedicated to pushing the boundaries of technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contacts-form/field_hidden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contacts-form/field_hidden/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customized Excellence in Software Development</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page-about-us/section-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page-about-us/section-2/</guid>
      <description>Our forte lies in crafting tailor-made software solutions that align precisely with your unique business challenges. With our profound expertise in creating advanced web-based applications, we transform your vision into reality. Trust ScalHive to guide your project from conception to completion with precision and flair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our mission</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page-index-first/section-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page-index-first/section-2/</guid>
      <description>To help our clients become real-time enterprises with systems that combine the scalability and resilience architecture with the real-time value of data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pipeline-Focused Data Engineers: Masters of Data Flow</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page-services/section-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page-services/section-2/</guid>
      <description>The creation and management of data pipelines are complex tasks that require Data Engineers with specialized skills in data modeling, ETL/ELT processes, SQL, and programming languages like Python, Scala, and Java.&#xA;At ScalHive, we don&amp;rsquo;t just find Pipeline-Focused Data Engineers; we find the right ones for you. Our rigorous vetting process considers your unique needs and demands, ensuring that we provide talent that is not only proven but also perfectly aligned with your objectives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contacts-form/field_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contacts-form/field_2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Engineering Expertise for Every Business Scale</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page-about-us/section-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page-about-us/section-3/</guid>
      <description>We empower businesses of all sizes by scaling their data engineering capabilities with top-tier talent. Our distinctive offshore staffing model, combined with a hands-on approach, guarantees the perfect match of expertise for your projects – efficiently, affordably, and within your timelines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Solutions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page-index-first/section-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page-index-first/section-3/</guid>
      <description>For:&#xA;Real-Time Analytics IoT Platforms Real-Time Personalization eCommerce Real-Time Financial Processes Application Modernization </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contacts-form/field_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contacts-form/field_3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive, Client-Focused Approach</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page-about-us/section-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page-about-us/section-4/</guid>
      <description>Our process begins with a deep understanding of your specific requirements. We then meticulously source, recruit, and integrate the ideal data engineers into your team. But our support doesn’t stop there – we ensure continuous management and assistance to keep your team productive, cohesive, and perfectly attuned to your business objectives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contacts-form/field_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contacts-form/field_4/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page-index-second/section-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page-index-second/section-4/</guid>
      <description>Rapid Values:&#xA;Swift Value Deployment Responsive Launch Solutions Developer Support &amp;amp; Assistance Expert Training Programs Talent Acquisition Guidance Reducing Risks:&#xA;Comprehensive Production and Development Support Embedded Engineering Excellence Thorough Code and Architecture Reviews Proven Proof Of Value Initiatives Time-Tested Technologies and Methodologies </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data: The Heartbeat of Digital Success</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page-about-us/section-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page-about-us/section-5/</guid>
      <description>At ScalHive, we&amp;rsquo;re not just passionate about software; we believe in the power of data as the cornerstone of digital success. Our commitment is to equip you with exceptional data engineering talent, enabling you to construct a world-class team. Together, let&amp;rsquo;s harness the potential of data to propel your business towards its goals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contacts-form/field_5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contacts-form/field_5/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contacts-form/field_7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contacts-form/field_7/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trank Based Development: Branch for release</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 10:02:57 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/post-2/</guid>
      <description>Original article Branch: only when necessary, on incompatible policy, late, and instead of freeze Laura Wingerd &amp;amp; Christopher Seiwald (1998’s High-Level SCM Best Practices white paper from Perforce) If a team is pushing production releases monthly, then they are also going to have to push bug-fix releases between planned releases. To facilitate that, it is common for Trunk-Based Development Teams to make a release branch on a just in time basis - say a few days before the release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trunk Based Development: Introduction</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:02:30 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/post-1/</guid>
      <description>Original article Introduction Trunk-Based Development is not a new branching model. The word ‘trunk’ is referent to the concept of a growing tree, where the fattest and longest span is the trunk, not the branches that radiate from it and are of more limited length. It has been a lesser known branching model of choice since the mid-nineties and considered tactically since the eighties. The largest of development organizations, like Google (as mentioned) and Facebook practice it at scale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contacts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contacts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contacts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/thank-you/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for message!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/</guid>
      <description>Modernizing businesses through innovative solutions, our expertise in data engineering, data science, big data analysis, and reactive application development forms the core for achieving ambitious goals with confidence and precision </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
